Everyone has heard of Hwata,
the legendary skilled physician.
(Hwata = Chinese: Hua Tuo)
Wounds, poisoning, chronic illnesses
of many decades,
there was nothing he could not cure.
But what was most amazing was
his talent for surgery.
Four patients with paralysis were
given general anesthesia,
then they were treated by having
their bodies split open and internal
organs removed.
At that same time, Jojo was
campaigning to unify the world.
(Jojo = Chinese: Cao Cao)
He suffered from a chronic illness
of excruciating headaches.
Hwata went into his room and cured him
easily using a few silver needles.
Jojo was so appreciative of Hwata's talent,
he wanted to make him his personal physician.
But Hwata fled instead.
He did not wish to spend his life
taking care of just one patient.
Jojo's men were ordered to pursue
Hwata and bring him back.
"You just need to follow me back
to meet the Prime Minister."
"You will enjoy endless wealth and
glory for your remaining days."
"If a dog isn't allowed to bark, then what's
the joy in having great wealth?"
"As long as you're willing to work
for the Prime Minister, the whole
world will sing your praises."
"See, Hwata is the miracle doctor who
saved Jojo, the man who rules the world."
"What if I say no?"
"Those who defy him can only die."
"It looks as though Jojo is
going to be remembered
as the one who killed Hwata, the man
who saved the lives of the world."
At that moment,
the sun in the heavens commanded
the wind and a portal opened.
Laughing and smiling...
Hwata entered into the portal.
-= Episode 1 =-
-= Year 1351 - near the border with Yuan =-
(Yuan Dynasty- Mongol's dynasty in China
1271-1368)
Over there... Is it Hwata?
There are people following us.
I know.
From the look of it, they're not peasants.
1. 2. 3.
Is the boat ready?
General!  There aren't any boats.
What are you talking about?
How can there not be
a single boat available?
There just isn't.
They said there isn't a single boat
that can sail right now.
They said they expect two boats to
return tomorrow afternoon.
We will have to stay here overnight.
What do you mean stay?
Why here?
Goryeo is just across the river.
Exactly why...
(Goryeo - Korea)
As you wish.
Then I will have things ready.
Look here, Wudalchi!  Wudalchi!
I say, Wudalchi!
We should go and find an inn for the night.
Innkeeper, my master just got
married recently.
But they are both extremely sensitive.
They wish only their own people
to take care of them.
Here, it's more than enough, right?
Just think of it as your lucky day.
Please go home and rest.
Yes.
Hurry and tell them all to leave.
It's closing time.
Finish eating and leave quickly.
Don't just stand there.
Customer, please.
What is this?
Let's go.
Do you think they got rid of the boats?
Probably.
Then do you think they also knew we
would have to spend the night at an inn?
You said this was the only inn.
So you knew that and still chose
to stay here?
Would you rather plant our flag
in an open field and wait for them
to attack us?
So how should we defend now?
Do it... very... well.
Yes.
Group A, close the windows and
block the doors using the tables.
The enemy arrived before us,
so we should be on high alert.
As soon as we arrive in Goryeo,
the first thing you should do is
kill that Wudalchi.
When I heard that this was the escort
sent from Goryeo to protect you, I
understood.
This is an insult!
Ten years.
Yes.  It's been more than 10 years
since Your Majesty has been home.
Yuan politely calls you a Prince of Goryeo.
When you were young, they forcibly
took you there and held you as hostage.
Finally, Your Majesty is now
able to return to Goryeo.
But what is the meaning of this?
They should be waving hundreds of flags,
with thousands of soldiers to escort you.
But what? You cannot wear your
dragon robes and cannot show your face?
We cannot call you "Your Majesty"!
Of all the ridiculous, disrespectful...
Those bastards should all...!
I will be bringing the Queen
to this room.
How dare you enter His Majesty's
quarters without knocking?
It is too difficult to guard multiple rooms.
I know that the two of you do not have
the best relationship, but please understand.
You bastard!
Do you know how to use a sword?
Please guard that window.
Guard... What do you mean
guard the window?
You...!
Where are you going?
You must stay near us so that we
can protect you.
I will take care of my own life.
There are more of them
than we expected.
Even if you are scared,
you must stay by my side.
Can you do that?
I will not run.
Then... I will be able to protect you.
Your Highness.
Catch them alive!
Don't let them get away!
Jang Bin.
General.
I will need some of your energy.
-=Applying energy to slow the
blood flow and the heartbeat=-
-=The energy flows with the blood.  If the
energy is stopped, the blood flow will stop.=-
Catch them!
Don't let even one of them escape!
Don't kill them!
I told you not to kill them.
What happened?
What is this?
Hey, didn't I tell you not to kill them,
you bastards?
I said we needed to find out
who sent them!  Didn't I say that?
That's not it.
What's not it?
These bastards.
They killed themselves!
Doctor!  Doctor!  Dr. Jang, have you
lost your senses?  What are you doing?
Just as you see, I'm currently
treating the wounded.
You first must save the Queen.
Don't you understand the situation now?
We could all end up dead!
Here, let's go right now!
- Pharmacist!
- Yes?
Come and take care of this.
This could be the end of our Goryeo.
Your Majesty, you know who our Queen is.
She is a Yuan princess.
How can we just let her die by
the roadside?
There have been rumors saying that
Goryeo will become a vassal state of Yuan.
What will happen if their princess
dies here?
This would be the opportunity they
are looking for,
that would let them
swallow Goryeo whole.
Is there no hope for her?
The large blood vessel in her neck
has been cut.
I've slowed the bleeding by reducing
the blood flow through acupuncture.
-=path through which the life-energy known as "qi" flows=-
I've slowed the bleeding by reducing
the blood flow through acupuncture.
-=path through which the life-energy known as "qi" flows=-
But it's only a temporary measure.
If the blood vessel is cut,
just put it back together!
It was very difficult to slow her pulse.
If we disturb the blood energy by moving her,
she may bleed to death quickly.
No... No... We must save her.
Only a Divine Healer would be
able to save her.
What? A Divine Healer?
If that woman dies, our country dies.
Wudalchi, what do you think?
I'm just a warrior,
so I don't deal in politics.
It looks like as soon as I become king,
the country is destroyed.
I'm quite a great king.
There is, Your Majesty,
a divine healer.
Very near here.
And I know where he is.
Where is he?
I'll have my men find him.
He is in Heaven, but I know where
the portal to the sky is.
Right over there.
That is Dr. Jang.
He is considered the best healer in Goryeo.
Even he said it's impossible, so we can
now only appeal to Heaven.
If we do, would the Heavens save her?
What's important is you must pray to
God with all your heart.
"The people were so sad to see
his profound grief."
"He fasted and prayed for her
continuously for 3 days and 3 nights."
These are the kind of things that
those in Yuan should hear about.
So you think we can hold back
their anger by doing all this?
This is all for Goryeo.
Then go and make the preparations.
You honor me.
Can Her Highness be moved?
No, she cannot.
I will divide the troops,
leaving most of the men here,
since it appears that their target
was the Queen.
Wudalchi.
It's very far from Goryeo to Yuan, right?
Yes, it's far.
What were you thinking along the way as
you escorted me over such a long distance?
I didn't really think much.
What I'm asking is,
how did you see me as a King?
To have a wise and benevolent king
is really fortunate for the people.
This is what I thought.
Should I say more?
You... don't like me.
Me?
You didn't like me even before
you met me, right?
Your Majesty, if I were to answer that,
then I would have to die.
Why do you hate me?
I am your King.
Just tell me truthfully.
Will you tell me if I make it
a royal command?
When the late Prince Gyeongchang
ascended the throne, he was only 14.
Because he was too young to fulfill
his duties, Yuan had him dethroned.
I know.
Your Majesty is 21 years old.
Whether 14 or 21, they're both
too young for a king.
Moreover, you have lived in Yuan
since the age of 10.
The Yuan way of thinking is in your bones.
"Our people of Goryeo are really unlucky
to have someone like this be the King."
That was what I was thinking.
That is all.
Everyone else probably thinks the
same way, right?
The people of Goryeo.
You're already the 5th King
in the past 12 years.
I doubt they thought much
about it at all.
For telling me your true feelings, thank you.
Your Majesty.
That means I don't especially dislike you.
-=King Gongmin, Goryeo's 31st King.=-
-=Choe Yeong, General of the
Wudalchi (Royal Guards) at the time.=-
Your Majesty.
It is said that this natural spring,
is the legendary portal through which
Hwata flew to the Heavens 1000 years ago.
While in the Heavens, Hwata has
nurtured many disciples.
Once every 300 years, his disciples
may enter our world through this portal.
That is how the legend goes.
In other words, you think we should
pray through this small opening?
It's not just an opening,
but a portal to the Heavens.
What is that?
Group B, be on your guard!
Group A, guard the outside!
Your Majesty, Heavens' gate is open!
Heavens' gate is open!
If you go through there, Your Majesty,
you will meet the Divine Healer, Hwata.
Your Majesty, please command
for him to come.
No matter if it's Hwata or
one of his disciples.
You must bring him before the
portal closes!
Quickly, Your Majesty!
Since you seem to know so much,
you should go.
You bastard.
The one who can save the Queen,
Heaven's Divine Healer is
in there, Your Majesty.
Even though I can't believe
everything he says...
Please give me your order.
We at least have to give it a try, right?
I will go.
General.
This is a royal order.
General!
Dae Man!
Hey. Did you see?
You saw it, right?
What?
Over there, someone came out.
You're seeing things.
Really. Look, look.
What?
-=2012, Seoul =-
=An alert has been issued due to a
multilevel sunspot explosion.=
=According to the report this afternoon
by the research institute,=
=so far there is no report of
any related damage.=
-=However, domestic airline flight
paths have been rerouted to avoid
damage from the cosmic storm=-
-=and are now using the Arctic route.=-
Master.
Excuse me, Master.
I have come from a different land.
My name is Choe Yeong.
A different land?
I know that I do not belong here,
but please help me.
How can I help you?
I'm looking for a Divine Healer.
Divine Healer?
I heard that Hwata came here.
Hwata...
Ah, a doctor, right?
Yes.
Doctors have many different specialties.
Internal medicine, surgeons, OB/GYN,
dentists.
Where is the problem?
This part.
That part... Ah, a plastic surgeon!
Do you know where they are?
There are a lot of plastic surgeons here.
This is Gangnam.
Not just any doctor,
It must be a Divine Healer.
You must be looking for a famous one.
Oh, I saw a banner.
There's a plastic surgery convention
at the COEX.
There should be a lot of famous
ones there.
CO...
COEX.
Which direction?
It's over there.
You see it?
If it's the one over there,
I was just there.
But...
how should I go there?
You can just... go.
I... just... go?
As expected.
Thank you for your lesson.
Master Hye Jeong, are they shooting
a candid camera bit in our temple?
If they were shooting a drama,
I would've known.
You don't know either?
Hello? Hello?
This lousy phone, what's wrong with it?
Just... go.
A technique that has been used since
the 70s to remove wrinkles,
the subcutaneous lift,
also called a minimal access
cranial suspension lift.
Just like that, an incision from
the scalp behind the ear
to the front of the ear.
We then pull the skin after separating it
from the subcutaneous layer,
(subcutaneous - the lowermost layer of skin)
and trim off the excess skin.
This shows how we separate the skin
from the subcutaneous layer.
If you're not very careful,
you might touch one of these
blood vessels.
You need be very focused here.
This is how we suture the skin closed.
This photo is 10 days after the surgery.
As you can see, there is a small scar.
Not only does the surgery leave a scar,
but it has many other flaws.
The most serious flaw is that
its effect doesn't last very long.
The patients who underwent this surgery...
They have had to return to the doctor
again in about 2 years.
Because they will have to do it again.
Next, I'll introduce the surgery
called the AccuLift.
It's been recognized worldwide as the
remedy to the problems with past procedures.
I don't know. I'm so unlucky.
Some idiot barged in and messed up
my whole presentation.
It's just not my day.
I woke up this morning with a
massive headache.
That petty Dr. O, only cares about the
male doctors, never me.
I really can't stand it anymore.
Just wait and see.
In 3 years' time, I will definitely
open a clinic in Gangnam.
Speaking of which,
how about investing in my clinic?
Rotten girl. Didn't you marry a rich man?
Spend some of that money!
Look here, ajussi.
Which of these companies hired
you for promotion?
Look here, ajussi!
I'm asking which company you're with.
Do you have an entrance pass?
Hey. Are you deaf?
Hey, Ajussi.
How can I go inside there?
I have to get inside.
Please open this for me.
This doctor inside here,
I have to meet her.
A doctor?
Are you playing with me?
We don't have time for fooling around.
These clothes...
What is this?
Is it ketchup?
Wow, look at this.
Wait wait wait wait,
let's talk.
Wait, wait.  I'm fine.
You... you just assaulted me.
Call the police quick!
Tell them there's a crazy man here
who's assaulting personnel and
damaging property.
And... that...
he's carrying an illegal weapon.
You're in so much trouble now.
You jerk!
Run! Run!
Oh Doctor, how are you?
Please come and take a look.
Doctor, these days you must have
state of the art equipment.
Please have a look at these.
This has an optical zoom of 2.5x.
It's manufactured using an ultra-light alloy.
You have no idea how great it is.
Some doctors have even forgotten to
take them off after an operation.
They just end up wearing them home.
And in the middle, there is an
LED light that flashes on and off...
Wow. These days some companies are
promoting using special methods.
So he's working dressed like that?
I thought he was an extra from a drama.
Look at that makeup.
He's coming over.
There's an urgent patient.
So?
According to our physician,
the vein on her neck was severed.
Can you save that patient?
Why are you asking me?
Doesn't he seem a bit strange?
I think he's trying to flirt with you.
Can you send me the brochure for this?
Of course.
Write down the address of your
hospital and I'll send it right over.
Okay.
That's him... him.
The sword on him is real.
Please put down your weapon!
Put down your weapon!
That patient, can you save them?
I'd have to see the patient first
before I know.
Where and how much the patient is hurt...
How much they are hurt...
You have to see for yourself?
Put the sword down!
Why did you have to follow me?
Her wound from the sword
looks just like this.
The depth is almost the same too.
Can you save him?
Ambulance! Quickly, call 119!
Yes.
If you can't save this person,
then I'll just try again, with him.
Please spare me!
You want me to save him?
This person?  Right here?
We don't have much time.
Please get started.
I need the proper instruments.
I need surgical clamps and hooks...
Oh God, our Father!
If you will spare me from death, I will...
Please hold this here...
Please forgive my sins and lead me
through this...
Yes?
If this person dies, you will be next.
What?
Ah! Yes, yes.
Mask.
Sterilize.
Ah, sterilize, sterilize.
I have stopped the bleeding with a clamp.
I need to suture it closed immediately,
so hold this.
=This is the Gangnam Police Force,
Officer Pak speaking.=
=What is the situation in there?
Is there anyone who can reply?=
=I will call the phone inside.
Please answer and talk to us.=
=I'm calling now.=
- Hey.  Isn't it done yet?
- Not yet.
The hostages are a man and a woman.
According to witnesses, he wounded a
security guard with a sword.
We believe he may be mentally ill.
We can't wait much longer because
the injured person's condition is not good.
Tie, cut.
You've worked hard.
Excuse me, are we done?
This man... is alive.
We will have to wait and see.
He also needs antibiotics.
He's alive! Look.  So the surgery
was successful, right?
I need you to come with me.
Me? Why?
You need to save a person.
Ajussi, it's been a long time since I
stopped being a surgeon.  Besides...
It may be difficult for you to enter
my world, so please stay behind me.
That, Ajussi, I...
Don't get lost, follow closely.
The suspect is coming out with the hostage.
Everyone get in your positions.
Why can't you just do as I say?
Go where?
There are police everywhere out there.
How are we going to get out?
We'll break through the front.
Lock down. Lock down!
They are going out!
Ajussi, wait. Ajussi, really...
Ajussi!
Ajussi, why don't you surrender, okay?
Please surrender!
Please forgive this discourtesy.
What do you mean?
Please spare me!
All you have to do is go in there.
Please let me go. Let me go.
I won't kill you.
As long as you save her,
I will bring you back.
Lies! I've seen your face already.
In movies, if you see the kidnapper's face,
you always get killed.  I know that!
I am Choe Yeong, a Goryeo warrior.
I swear on my life and my honor as
a warrior, I'll send you back if you save her.
I promise.
-=Seoul. 10 days ago=-
So, what do you want to know?
A man.  My man.
When and where will I meet him?
May I have your date of birth?
This is my name and birth date.
But not just any man.
He must have lots of money.
If I asked you for next week's winning
Lotto numbers, would you tell me?
Of course not.
I would have already done it if I could.
As I was saying, when and where
will I meet a rich man?
Okay... Okay...
-=Incantation=-
If possible, it would be nice if
he was warm and kind.
But a rich man doesn't have to
be ugly, right?
You were born on May 5th?
There will be light shining between
Heaven and Earth.
You will only meet that man during that time.
The one who will fulfill your wishes.
What is it?
Where will I meet him?
It would be better if it can be as soon
as possible.  I kind of need money.
But it's not for brand name bags
or anything.
I'm in a middle of a research project,
regarding stem cell extraction.
And it's at the crucial period now,
but all the research funds have been exhausted.
Wow! Hey... This is incredible.
Give me your hand.
What is it?
What this divination is saying,
it's saying...
I have to look at the book.
This type of divination is unique.
Let me take a look.
He is the man sent from Heaven.
Omo, omo. A man sent from Heaven?
(Omo - Oh my)
But...
But?
He is a man from the past.
From the past?
Think about men you have dated before.
Sorry?
The man that Heaven sent you
must be among them.
That is what the divination said.
Do you mean...
During my student and intern period,
there was a man I dated
for 3 years and 4 months,
my seonbae.
(seonbae - senior, mentor)
He had me do his graduate
thesis when he was a senior.
Seonbae, you were on night duty,
so you haven't had breakfast, right?
I brought you some food.
I made it myself.
Wait.  Which is the tuna?
No, not this.  This is radish. This is it.
Eun Su.
You want this?
I'm sorry.
You've eaten already?
I have another woman.
Her family is very rich, and she
said she will open a clinic for me.
Exactly how rich?
I heard that they have
several buildings in Gangnam.
Oh...
That woman is much uglier than you,
and her personality is bad, too.
But what can I do?
She's building a clinic for me.
Sorry.
I'm leaving first.
The second man I think really liked me.
Whenever he saw me, he would nearly die.
Here and here, we can fill it
up a bit more.
We can do a little bone shaving here.
Don't worry, we'll use general anesthesia.
Do you want some botox injections?
If you want a V-line in your face, then---
Dr. Yu.
Yes?
Eun Su.
I think we dated for about 3 months?
So then?
I couldn't do it anymore.
Even if he was rich, I just couldn't bear it.
Didn't you say you wanted a rich man?
It wouldn't be him, right?
A man sent from Heaven...
Sent for you by Heaven.
To be honest, I don't want to
get married yet.
Just getting engaged will be good enough.
If I get the money, I can finish
my research project.
There's a company that will purchase
the patent.
If that happens, then I can repay the
loan and cancel the engagement.
That would really be awesome!
But, that's not going to happen.
Why not?
Let's try the next divination.
-=The Hexagram Sequence=-
The pronunciation of this sign
is really difficult.
It says, you will soon go on a
long journey for one year.
Where would I go?
I barely got this job at this hospital.
How can I just leave?
In other words, this divination
is a travel sign.
This is an auspicious sign.
You will meet him if you go through
the doorway.  You will only achieve
this after you meet him.
So what I want to know is about that man.
That rich man, where and
how do I meet him?
It's already been arranged
by the Heavens.
There are so many people who never
get to meet their Heaven-sent person.
So many... it's uncountable.
Really...
Forget it. I'm going.
This person...
Think hard. Try to remember.
Try to remember.
Perhaps a brief encounter among
the sea of people from your past.
I heard in this building,
there is an amazing tarot master.
Do you know where he is?
Oh, that question was a bit rude.
I'm sorry, I'll leave.
Man from the past?
Does he think I'm an idiot?
Such a swindler.  Seriously.
-=7 years ago (Goryeo period)=-
Have you heard?
The newly appointed leader of
the Wudalchi is...
His age...
He is only...
He is only 22 years old.
But he was the leader of the Joekwoldae.
But, there are rumors that our new
General has some impressive skills.
Killing 3 enemies with 1
swing of his sword.
Astonishing levitation.
He can jump over a city wall
with one leap.
You've all heard that the Joekwoldae
people have special powers?
It is said that our new General
has a lightning power,
where lightning bolts shoot
from his hands.
It is also said that he has a
nasty temper.
There was once someone who
woke him from his sleep,
and he nearly killed him.
Kid, that's just a tall tale.
To be honest,
people from the Joekwoldae kill their
enemies just by sneaking up on them.
You can't say that.
They have killed many many
enemy commanders.
And you're really willing
to give that General spot to a
kid who's still so green?
He's was personally appointed by the King.
Rumor has it,
that he wasn't appointed because
the King favors him,
but because he wanted him to suffer.
Shut up.
None of you know anything
about the Joekwoldae.
Because of the Joekwoldae, our Goryeo
is still standing.
Aigoo. Seriously.
Deputy General, you just sit and watch.
When he comes, watch how I
kick his butt.
Please identify yourself.
Didn't you hear our
Deputy General's question?
Who are you?
Are you ignoring me?
Are you the one in charge here?
I am Wudalchi's Deputy General,
Bae Chung Seok. You are?
Where do I sleep?
What?
They said I would get it when
I came here...
my bed.
He got here the day before yesterday, right?
For 3 days and 2 nights he has
done nothing but sleep, not eating.
Right. He hasn't even had to pee.
Do you think he's dead?
I heard that people die in their sleep.
I put my hand under his nose to see
if he was still breathing, and he is.
Deol Bae.
Those rumors. Are they true?
What rumors?
That person who only sleeps,
can he really kill 3 people with 1 swing,
leap over a high wall with a jump,
and shoot lightning from his hands?
How can such person exist in this world?
He does.
Those are just rumors.
Go wake him up.
I don't care if he's the new general or
not, I'm going to try fighting him.
Don't! What if you really wake him?
Didn't you hear that he nearly beat
a man to death for waking him up?
Deok Man, get out of the way.
-=Next Episode Preview=-
I, as a warrior for this country,
think that you as a King should have some
form of self-discipline.
That is what I believe.
Can I believe that,
the Heavens are still protecting this country?
That person is really weird.
Can you speak English?
How do you do? Thank you.
Telephone.
Phone.
How can the village studio be so big?
Catch that woman!
Who dares to ignore me?
Come out. Come out now!
After considering over and over again,
I still believe they are insignificant.
Since we have already started,
we should walk through the end.